John Croker - Web Developer

Address: Poulton le Fylde, Lancashire, UK

Mobile: +44 7462 286764 Email: jj.croker@gmail.com Website: johncroker.me

I am a full-stack web developer with 4 years experience designing and building web applications including SPAs, Customer Relationship Management (CRM) back-ends as well as news blogs and more. I am constantly refreshing my skills to keep up with ongoing trends and ensure I write code to a high standard.

Relevant Skills/Experience

Front-end

- HTML5, Blade, Handlebars
- Es7, Vue, React
- Vuex, Redux
- SCSS, LESS, BEM
- Gulp, Webpack, Babel

Back end

- PHP, Laravel
- Node.js, Express
- MS SQL, MySQL, MongoDB
- Windows Server/IIS

Cloud (AWS)

- dynamodb
- lambda

Relevant Experience

Web Developer - Barcadia Media (2015 - present)

Designed and developed several client-facing and internal web applications with Vue/Vuex front-ends and PHP (Laravel) back-ends. I also lead our team to adopt more Agile development practices

Freelance Web Developer - Buxton Web Design Ltd. (2015)

Front-end development on WordPress websites.

Freelance Web Developer - BBPN ltd. (2014 - 2015)

Created WordPress plugins for a company CMS.

Education

Lancaster University (2011 - 2014)

BSc (Hons) in Computer Science - First Class Honours

Blackpool and Fylde College (2009 - 2011)

IT Practitioner BTEC Diploma (Distinction)

References

Andy Shields - Director - Barcadia Media

- → andy@barcadiamedia.co.uk
- **→** 01253 272998